<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction GenGPT-X</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Introduction GenGPT-X</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2023 Xueshan Chen</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 10:33:37 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tracker</title>
      <link>https://example.com/tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 02:59:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/tracker/</guid>
      <description>This is the help of tracker &amp;ndash; An android app to track your outdoor activities.
You can contact me via email
index The index page have the main functionalities of this app.
 Start: user can start track their activities by click this button Setting &amp;amp; Help menu, on the top left corner, user can visit these two buttons at any page View History: user can view the recoded histories of their activities, which was stored in the database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 10:00:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/intro/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Setup</title>
      <link>https://example.com/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/setup/</guid>
      <description>Project Structure There are two parts in this project. The front end and the back end. Both are located in the root of this project. Demostration Video of Website is the presentation and description of the website, the structure of the front and back ends will be explained in the section after this document.
User Manual In this section, a tutorial on the use of this website and the basic setup of this project will be presented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://example.com/tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Website Tutorial Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time to use the features brought by the GenGPT-X.
In this section, we will show how to use this website. There is also the option of watching a video presentation via Youtube.
Firstly, the user can choose from three ways of generating GPTs, as follows:
The GPT can be generated by selecting an actual example or by choosing to use GenGPT or GenGPT-X, respectively. The user is asked to enter the relevant parameters when choosing to generate the GPT using the generator, as shown below (Figure \ref{para-set}).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
